Okay, guys, listen.
好，大家注意听
Tomorrow, Emily gets married again.
明天是艾蜜莉再婚的日子
So try to really keep Ross' mind off of it.
我们要尽全力 转移罗斯的注意力
Good idea.
对，好主意
Hey,man. What's up?
你怎么了？
Just thinking about Emily getting married tomorrow.
正在想艾蜜莉明天结婚的事
Oh,Ross! Look,look!
罗斯，你看
What? Where?
看什么？在哪里？
Right over there! There! Look,look,look!
就在那儿啊，快看…
-What am I looking at? -Somebody help me out here.
你要我看什么？ 谁来帮帮我啊
Hey!
你们好吗？
Monica,sorry I didn't come by. I was out with Gary.
摩妮卡，抱歉我昨晚没过去 我跟盖瑞在一起
He let me ride around with him. We saw and prevented crimes.
他用警车载我去兜风 我们还阻止了一起犯罪
You got to go on a ride-along?
你可以坐警车去兜风？
-I want to go on a ride-along! -Me too!
我也要坐警车兜风 我也是
-Okay. -Yeah! Me too!
好啊 我也要
Really? You?
你真的要？
Yeah.
是啊
-Well,it's kind of dangerous. -Well,I like danger.
有点危险喔 我喜欢危险
-Okay, you guys free tonight? -Yeah!
好，你们今天晚上有空吗？ 有…
You didn't say it was gonna be at nighttime.
今晚？你刚才没说是在晚上
The One With the Ride-Along
本集播出：“抢救三明治”
rainystar压制iPod-MP4
I'm so glad you're home. We can finally organize these photos.
真高兴你回家了 今晚总算能整理这些相片
Oh,thank God!
谢天谢地
Finally!
终于！
I've broken them down into categories.
我已经把照片分门别类
We got holidays, birthdays, candids....
有假日类、生日和偷拍
And I've cross-referenced them by subject.
我已经依照主题 做好了交叉搜寻
So if you're looking up,say...
好比你要找...
...birthdays and dogs, you get photo 152.
...生日和狗 就会找到152号相片
See?
你看
Oh,it's me and LePoo.
是我和拉普
Wow,I miss that dog.
我真怀念那条狗
You can also find him under "dog" and "dead."
你也能在狗和死亡项目之中 找到拉普
Great. Thanks.
太好了，多谢
Hand me that other box of photos. That's the last one.
把另一箱照片递给我 那是最后一箱
Oops.
糟糕
Sorry.
对不起啦
Good thing you numbered them.
幸好你有写上号码，对吧？
I hadn't.
还没
Photo 152 was a prototype.
152号相片是范例
Honey, it's okay. It's okay.
别难过…
How about I fix you a drink? Maybe a margarita?
我帮你弄杯喝的 玛格莉特好吗？
Ross has the blender.
果汁机在罗斯那里
Everything's just falling apart.
一切都毁了
It's okay. I'll go to Ross', get the blender.
亲爱的，不碍事 我去找罗斯拿果汁机
-You get the margarita stuff ready. -All right.
你先准备玛格莉特的材料 好吧
His keys are in the drawer. Also,I need some cash.
他家钥匙放在抽屉里 我还需要一些现金
Want me to stop at the ATM?
你要我去自动柜员机取吗？
No. While you're at Ross', if you see any lying around.
不用，到罗斯家里拿就好
-What? -What?
什么？ 什么？
I don't do that.
我不做那种事的
That was so cool,man. The way you leaned on that guy.
你逼问那家伙的方式 真是太酷了
It is starting to get dark out there.
天色越来越黑了
He told you everything. You cracked him.
他什么都招了 他对你毫不保留
He was the victim. They're usually pretty talkative.
对，他是受害者 他们通常都很多话
Okay, but it is officially nighttime.
好，正式进入夜晚了
-Want me to grab the berry for you? -It's called a cherry.
盖瑞，要我帮你拿红灯吗？  这叫做“警灯”
It's called Chandler!
这叫做“警灯”
Okay,I got it.
买到了
This place makes the best sandwich in the world.
这家店做的三明治 世界第一
Does it have meatballs?
乔伊，里头有肉球吗？
Oh,yeah.
没错
Melted cheese and marinara sauce?
有融化的起司 和大蒜番茄酱吗？
Yep.
有
You can't eat that in my car.
那就不能在我的车上吃
Yeah,okay.
好吧
Even though my tax dollars paid for this car.
买这部警车的钱 我缴的税也有一份
Your tax dollars?
你缴的税？
Yeah,okay.
好啦（你缴的税）
Wow,that sandwich smells good.
这个三明治还真香
Did I say you could smell it?
我有说你可以闻吗？
I can't smell it?
闻个三明治都不行？
Half the taste is in the smell. You're sucking up all the taste units.
香味就兹チ撕贸缘囊话 你把好吃都吸光了
Okay,I'll give them back.
好吧，还给你
What is so great about that sandwich?
这三明治到底棒在哪里？
Imagine the best sex you ever had.
想想你做爱最爽的一次 好
-Are you thinking about Monica? -Yeah.
你想的是摩妮卡吗？ 是啊
What's that like?
是什么感觉？
Please don't be from a real dinosaur. Please,please.
拜托不要是真的恐龙
Please,please.
千万不要…
"Made in Mexico." Yes!
墨西哥制造，好耶
Who would buy this?
谁会买这种东西？
Rach, it's me. Pick up!
瑞秋，是我，快接啊
What's up?
什么事？
I need a few more things for the margaritas.
我做玛格莉特还缺材料
I need some salt, some margarita mix and tequila.
我要盐巴、玛格莉特调汁 还有龙舌m酒
So all we had was ice?
我们家里只有冰块喔？
See if he has ice.
看看他有没有冰块
好吧
Hello,Ross?
罗斯
It's Emily here.
我是艾蜜莉
I know this is out of the blue, but I'm getting married tomorrow.
我知道这很突然 但是我明天就要结婚了
Well,maybe I am....
或许啦… 我...
I keep thinking about you.
我一直在想你
And I'm wondering if we made a mistake giving up so fast.
不知道我们太快放弃 是不是一个错误
Are you thinking about me?
你有在想我吗？
No,of course you're not. But if you are,call me tonight.
一定没有 如果有的话 今晚打给我
Okay, bye.
好吧，再见
Where we going?
下一站是哪里？
This witness won't return my calls. We'll surprise him coming home.
这个目击证人不回我电话 我们去他家堵他
Surprise him? We're not gonna make anybody mad,are we?
去堵他？他不会生气吧？
Come on, man.
得了吧你
You gonna squeeze the perp's shoes a bit before he lawyers up?
那你会在那贼人的律师出现前 先从他身上挤出一些汁来？
He's a witness, not a perp. And no one talks like that.
那是目击证人，不是贼人 而且没有人会那样说话
Yeah. No one talks like that.
是啊，没人会那样说话
-Oh,what,like you're Mr. Cop? -I'm more cop than you two.
难不成你是警察？ 我比你们两个都像警察
How do you figure that?
这是什么道理？
I'm in the front seat,okay?
醒醒吧，我坐在前座
I'm Gary's partner.
我是盖瑞的搭档
When you say "partner," it doesn't sound cop.
你说搭档的时候不像警察
It sounds gay.
倒像是同志
Jealous.
爱吃醋
-Hey,we're undercover here. -Oh,yeah. No problem.
我们这是秘密出勤 好，没问题
-Ross! -Sorry.
罗斯 抱歉…
There.
好了
Hey,Gary. Who am l?
盖瑞，我是谁？
Phone home.
打电话回家
Look at Officer Ross riding back here with the visitors.
看看这位罗斯警官 被打入后座了
What's up with that,Serpico?
是啊，
"What's up with that,Serpico?"
这是怎么一回事呢？
Are you thinking about me? No,of course you're not.
你有在想我吗？ 一定没有
But if you are,call me tonight.
如果有的话，今晚打给我
Okay,bye.
好吧，再见
No.
不会吧
I know!
我知道
Thank God you were here. We have to erase that.
幸好先被你听到了 我们一定要把这留言洗掉
What? We can't do that.
什么？我们不能那样
We have to. What if Ross hears that...
非这样不可 万一罗斯听到了
...and calls her back and they get back together?
回电给她 他们又复合了怎么办？
Is that what you want? Ross back with that controlling...
你希望那样吗？ 看到罗斯跟那个控制欲超强
...neurotic,crazy Emily? The Emily that wouldn't let him see you?
神经兮兮的疯子艾蜜莉复合？ 那个不让罗斯见你的艾蜜莉？
No! Oh,no,no.
不行，万万不可…
God,no! He should not get back with her.
罗斯绝对不能和她复合
I know that,you know that. Even Ross knows that.
你知我知，就连罗斯都知道
But we have no right to erase his message.
但我们还是没有权力 擅自洗掉给罗斯的留言
Look,I'm his sister and I love him. I don't want to see him get hurt.
我可是他的妹妹 我爱他，不想看他受到伤害
Doesn't that give me the right to control him?
得了 我这样还没有权控制…
Help him?
帮助他吗？
He's not the one who needs help.
我觉得需要帮忙的不是他
She's obviously unstable.
艾蜜莉非常不稳定
She's thinking about running out on her wedding day.
她竟然想在结婚当天落跑
Okay,fine. But look at the position she's putting him in.
好啦，但你看看 她让罗斯陷入了什么处境
And what's he gonna do?
你要罗斯怎么办？
Run over there on the wedding day and break up the marriage?
难不成在艾蜜莉结婚当天 跑去破坏婚礼？
Who would do that?
谁做得出那种事？
Okay,fine. All right. But that was different.
好啦，不过这是两码子事
Although it did involve a lot of the same people.
虽然有很多人都是重复的
This is some twisted joke she's playing on him.
艾蜜莉显然想用变态的笑话 来恶整罗斯
You are crazy. She sounded genuinely upset.
够了，你疯了 她听起来真的很沮丧
I mean,listen.
你听听就知道
Your messages have been erased.
您的留言已经清除
No!
不会吧…
Well,that worked out well. Margarita?
这样就省事多了 来杯玛格莉特？
Okay,but we're safe, right? Nothing bad's gonna go down.
我们很安全，对吧？ 不可能会有厄运降临
No. But that reminds me. Sign this.
对，不过我倒想起来了 签一下这个
What is it?
这是什么？
It just says you can't sue if you scrape your knee...
没什么，只是不能告到市政府头上 就算断腿...
...or get your head blown off.
...或者脑袋开花
Oh,hurry up. I want to sign that.
快点喔，我要签
Here he comes.
好，他来了
What is he doing? What the hell is he doing?
他在干嘛？搞什么鬼？
What is it?
什么？…怎么了？
-ls everything okay? -What?
没事吧？ 发生什么事？
He sees us. Don't move. And don't look at him!
他看到我们了，别动 不要看他
Hey,it's okay. It was just a car backfire.
没事的，只是车子逆火
Hey, look at that. You tried to save your buddy.
看看，你想用身体掩护朋友
You see that?
你看到了没？
You see what he did?
看到他冒命拯救朋友没？
You okay,man?
你没事吧？
Thanks,Joey.
乔伊，谢了
Hello?
那我呢？
Hi.
嗨
You all right?
没事吧？
We should go.
我们应该走了
No,wait.
等等…
Oh,yeah. Right.
对，钱拿走
No. Monica.
不是啦，摩妮卡…
Monica,we have to fix this.
摩妮卡，我们得补救这个
What can we do? You erased the message.
我们无能为力啊 你已经把留言洗掉了
Yeah,but maybe I could call his machine and re-create the message.
或许我可以再打电话进来 重新假造一段同样的留言
All right,okay....
我来试试…
Hello,Ross,this is Rachel Emily.
罗斯，我是瑞秋…艾蜜莉
God,what is it with those two names?
天啊 我怎么连名字都说不好
I do so wanted to say that I'm going to be getting married...
我打来只是要说我就快要…
...to another British person.
跟另外一个英国人结婚了
And I'm having doubts and scones....
我心里很疑惑…
-I can't remember what she said. -Yeah,that's the problem with this plan.
我忘记她说了什么 是啊，计划的问题就在这里
Rachel,come on. The message is erased, there's nothing we can do.
瑞秋，留言已经洗掉了 我们无能为力
He's never gonna find out.
罗斯永远不会发现的
I could tell him about it.
我可以老实跟他说啊
If you want to be rational, I can't argue with you.
如果你想要这么明理的话 我也争不过你
All right?
好啦
Fine,tell him. I just don't want to be a part of it.
你要说就说 我不想介入
Maybe that's Emily leaving the exact same message.
或许又是艾蜜莉打来的 她想说一样的话
Hey,Ross,it's you. I just want you to remember this feeling.
罗斯，是你啊 我只是要你记得这种感觉
You are lucky to be alive.
活着是一种幸运
So live every day to the fullest.
所以每一天都要活得精彩
Love yourself, okay?
珍爱自己，好吗？
And also get stamps. Bye.
好吧，也别忘了买邮票，再见
Play that message for Emily, and this problem goes away.
只要把这留言放给艾蜜莉听 所有的问题就都解决了
Right?
是吗？
Anybody want to meet a hero?
谁要来见见英雄？
John Glenn is here?
约翰葛林来了？
No. Joey.
不，是乔伊
Joey's never been in outer space.
乔伊没有上过太空啊
We had the most incredible night.
菲比，今晚真是太不可思议了
-We're in the car -Wait. Hold on.
我们在警车里… 慢着…
-Hi. -Hi.
嗨 嗨
Okay,go ahead.
好，继续说
So we're in the car,and bang! A shot was fired.
好…我们在警车里 突然缫簧 有人开枪
And Joey,with no regard for his own safety...
乔伊完全不顾自己的安危
...throws himself on me.
扑到我身上保护我
My God!
天啊，乔伊
It was a car backfire.
那是汽车逆火放屁的声音
But he didn't know that.
对，但是当时他并不知道
Yeah,I didn't know that.
对，我不知道
It could just as easily have been a bullet.
那很有可能会是子弹的
Ever think about joining the force? We could use a guy like you.
乔伊，有没有想过要当警察？ 警界很需要你这种人
Who jumps at loud noises.
听到巨响就吓得跳起来
Wow. I could have died tonight.
我今晚有可能丧命的
Yeah,if the car that backfired had run over you!
对，如果那部放屁的车 把你碾过去的话
I'm gonna go home,before Ross starts rambling about his newfound respect for life.
我先回家去了 省得罗斯大谈人生新发现
I do have a newfound respect for life.
我的人生的确有了新发现
Oh,my God!
天啊
Ross,I could have told you you weren't gonna die today.
罗斯，我早该跟你说 你今天不会有死劫的
What? You know when I'm gonna die?
你知道我为什么会死？
-You want to get some dinner? -Sure.
亲爱的，你要吃晚餐吗？ 好啊，当然
You know what? If I heard a shot right now, I'd throw my body on you.
你知道吗，若现在听到枪声 我一定会扑倒你身上
Maybe we should walk in a bad neighborhood.
是吗？那我们或许应该 去穷凶恶极的社区散步
Okay.
好
Bye.
再见 再见
Cut it out.
罗斯，你别再闹了
I'd hate to save your life and kick your ass on the same day.
我不想在同一天里 先是救你又痛扁你一顿
Why'd you take off?
你刚才怎么先闪了？
Just going for a walk.
我只是去散步
Around the living room,whatever.
在客厅里绕来绕去
-ls something wrong? -No. No,I'm just tired.
有什么不对吗？ 没有，我只是累了
You know,from the walk.
走路走累了
You dove in front of Ross!
好吧 你扑上去救罗斯
Ross!
罗斯耶！
That's what this is about.
原来是这么一回事
Oh,my God. You hate Ross!
天啊，你恨罗斯
I don't hate Ross.
我没有恨罗斯
Of course you do. I saved him. You're mad at me. It adds up.
你当然有！ 我救了他，你生我的气 这样全都说得通了
You want Ross out of the picture.
你想铲除罗斯？
What picture?
铲除什么？
I don't know. But I don't like what I'm hearing.
不知道，但是你说的话很吓人
I'm glad you saved Ross in the car backfire. But it could've been a bullet.
我很高兴你在汽车放屁事件中 救了罗斯一命 但那若真的是子弹怎么办？
And you didn't try to save me.
你竟然救他不救我
You're upset because you think I chose Ross over you.
原来你是在气这个 你以为我觉得罗斯比你重要
No,I knew you could take care of yourself.
不是这样的… 我知道你能照顾自己
You know? I mean,Ross needs help. He's not "street" like us.
罗斯需要别人帮忙 他不像你我见过大场面
You'd risk your life for Ross before you would for me.
话说到头，你宁愿先去救罗斯 也不来救我
That's the bottom line.
这才是重点
No,not exactly.
不完全是这样
All right,look.
好吧，好吧
I wasn't trying to save Ross.
其实我那不是要救罗斯
Okay?
My sandwich was next to Ross.
我的三明治在罗斯旁边
All right?
I was trying to save my sandwich.
我是要救我的三明治
From a bullet?
怕它被枪打到？
-I know it doesn't make much sense. -"Much" sense?
我知道这说来没啥道理… 岂止没啥道理
Look,it was instinct! I just went for it.
钱德，那是本能反应 当下就扑过去了
You risked your life for a sandwich?
所以你冒命去救三明治
I know it sounds crazy...
我知道这听起来很夸张
...but this is the greatest sandwich in the world!
但这可是世界上最棒的三明治
So you didn't choose Ross before me?
所以你并不觉得罗斯比我重要
No. I would never do that.
是啊，我绝对不会那样
You're like my brother.
你就像是我的亲兄弟
-Really? -Yeah.
真的？ 对
In fact,to prove how much you mean to me....
为了证明你对我的意义
Here.
给你
-Thanks. -Easy, it's not a hot dog!
谢了 轻一点，这不是热狗
How good is that?
是不是很好吃？
See?
看吧
What are you doing?
慢着，你在干嘛？
You're showing me how much I mean to you.
你不是要证明我对你的意义？
With a bite.
是啊，咬一口来证明
Jeez!
你也帮帮忙
嗨
What are you doing here?
瑞秋，你在这里干嘛？
Hey,you know what?
You are in our apartment all the time!
你动不动就往我们的公寓跑
This is just a drop in the bucket,mister!
我这只是小巫见大巫而已
It doesn't matter. The important thing is that you're here.
没关系啦，重点是你来了
You're my friend and you're here.
你是我朋友，而你来到了这里
Okay,just a little scared. What's going on?
好，我有一点点害怕 罗斯，你是怎么了？
The most amazing thing happened tonight.
今晚发生了最不寻常的事
I thought my number was up.
我还以为自己要去见阎王了
I had an actual near-death experience.
我真正面临到了濒死经验
What happened?
什么？…怎么回事？
We were on the ride-along with Gary and somebody took a shot at me!
我们不是跟盖瑞 坐警车兜风吗？ 有人朝我开枪！
Really?
真的吗？
No. A car backfired.
不是，是车子放屁
But I thought somebody was taking a shot at me. And,Rach...
但我当时以为是有人对我开枪 瑞秋
...I survived!
我劫后余生
And I was filled with this great respect for life.
我的人生拥有了全新视野
I want to experience every moment.
我要真切体验每一刻
I want to seize every opportunity.
我要把握每一个机会
I am seeing everything so clearly now.
现在的一切都变得好清晰
Because a car backfired?
全都是因为汽车放屁？
Okay. Why are you here?
好吧，你来这里干嘛？
I don't know how this fits into your whole "seizing" thing...
我不知道这件事符不符合 你所谓的“把握今朝”
...but Emily called you today.
不过艾蜜莉今天打了电话给你
-You talked to her? -She left a message.
你跟她说了话？ 没有，她在你电话里留言
But it kind of got erased.
不过留言被洗掉了
I mean,there's something wrong with your machine.
你的答录机有问题
What did she say?
那她说了什么？
Something about having second thoughts about the wedding...
说什么对结婚的事有点反悔
...and did you guys make a mistake breaking up?
说你们分手是个错误
And she wants you to call her.
她要你回电
Wow.
That was a good thing that I told you, right?
我跟你说这件事很对吧？
Yeah. Yes. Of course.
是啊，当然是这样
Okay,thank you. Thank you. Because
谢谢你… 谢谢 因为...
I'm gonna go tell Monica I was right.
我要去跟摩妮卡说 我这样做是对的
Because she didn't want
因为你知道吗？她不希望…
Not important. Point is, I was right. Your decision.
那不重要 重点是我是对的，你自己决定
Okay?
I was right.
我是对的
Your decision.
你自己决定要不要回电
Right.
对
I guess I should call Emily.
我猜我应该回电给艾蜜莉
No, that's not the right decision.
不对，你的决定不对…
That's not right.
这样不对
Ross,come on!
罗斯，你清醒一点
I mean...
我是说...
...that woman made you miserable!
...那个女人把你给整惨了
Do you really want to get back into that?
罗斯，你真的想要再来一次？
Okay,look. Yesterday...
如果她是在昨天打来的
...I wouldn't have even considered calling her back.
我压根不会想回电
But my ex-wife calls on the same day...
但在我面对濒死经验的同一天
...I have a near-death experience?
我的前妻正好打电话来
That's gotta mean something.
这一定有所含意
That was not a near-death experience. That was barely an experience.
罗斯，那不是濒死经验 就连经验都谈不上了
You weren't there!
当时你并不在场
Maybe this is something that I'm supposed to seize, you know?
或许这就是我应该把握的事
Okay. You know what?
好吧，你知道吗？
Maybe this is not about seizing stuff.
或许这无关把握或是不把握
Maybe this is about escaping stuff.
或许这是关于逃避
Okay? Look at today.
就拿今天来说
I mean,you escaped...
你逃过了…
...death.
死忘
And maybe this is a chance for you to escape...
或许这是你逃避机会
...getting back together with Emily.
不去和艾蜜莉复合
That does make sense.
这还蛮有道理的
Because I do want to seize some opportunity...
因为我要把握住这个机会
...but I really don't want to see or talk to her.
不和她见面或联络
Well,there you go!
这不就结了
Yeah,maybe today's just...
或许今天只是...
..."close call" day.
...“千钧一发”日
Hey, thanks, Rach.
瑞秋，谢了
Oh, honey. No problem.
亲爱的，甭客气
Wait, wait. The message is blinking.
等等…留言灯号在闪
Maybe you didn't erase it.
或许留言没被洗掉
Hey,Ross,it's you
罗斯，是你啊
That's an old message. Nobody needs to hear that.
这是旧的留言 没什么好听的 没错
-Hey,was Monica here? -Yeah.
摩妮卡有来过吗？ 有啊
I want my money back.
要她把我的钱还来
You probably need that for stamps, right?
是要用来买邮票的吧？
Has Gary ever been shot at for real?
菲比，盖瑞有真的中枪过吗？
Yes,once.
有，一次
A little.
小小的一次
He kind of did it to himself.
算是他自己打的
It's not really a good story.
这故事没什么好讲的
I wonder how I'd react under fire. And not backfire...
不知道我置身战火会怎样 不是汽车放屁
...but heavy fire.
是枪林弹雨
Like,if I was in a war.
好比我在战场上之类的
Man,I would be great in a war!
我去打仗一定很厉害
I think I'd make a fantastic military leader.
一定会是很棒的军事领袖
I mean,I know I'd make general before any of you guys.
跟你们这些人比起来 我一定会最先当上将军
Before or after you were shot by your own troops?
在你被自己的部下枪杀前 还是之后？
I know Joey would be in the foxhole protecting all of us.
我知道乔伊一定会在散兵坑里保护大家
If the foxhole was lined with sandwiches.
对，如果那个散兵坑 是用三明治围起来的话
Yeah, hero sandwiches.
没错，英雄三明治
You all know I'm a pacifist, so I'm not interested in war in any way.
你们知道我主张和平 我对什么战争都没兴趣
But when the revolution comes, I'll have to destroy you all.
不过等到革命的那一天来临 我一定要把你们消灭光光
Not you, Joey.
乔伊，你例外